剧情回顾...
-你确定要这么做么  -我决定了
-Are you sure you really want to?  -I've made my choice.
它从哪来的?
Where's it come from?
从里边的地图上看  是尼日利亚
Based on the maps, Nigeria.
飞机上有人么?
Anyone on board?
有两个穿着像牧师的人
Two men dressed as priests.
牧师?
Priests?
实际上是伪装后的毒贩子
Drug runners in disguise.
飞机上全是海洛因
The plane was loaded with heroin.
你是谁?
我是Micheal
爸爸?
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Singa校对：扣扣
后期：xyz 双语制作：DrunkBat neo19 七色九天
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
抓住孩子
你们大家跟我们走
安静点
你们都给我离开
住手   别带走孩子了
抓住那个老人
-抓住那个小的  -对  就是那个小的
不  不  不
放手
Let him go!
杀了他
Kill him.
马上给我开枪
Shoot him. Now.
开枪
Shoot him!
Do it.
小子  你叫什么?
What's your name, boy?
你叫什么?
Eko
看看Eko先生
Look at Mr Eko.
一点也不犹豫
No hesitation.
天生的杀手
A born killer.
来吧
Come.
你不再需要那东西了
You won't need that anymore.
回去了
Back.
回去了  回去了
Back we go, back we go.
你在写什么?
What are you writing?
我需要记得的东西
Things I need to remember.
不介意我坐下吧?
Do you mind if I sit?
请坐
Please.
谢谢
Thanks.
你叫Eko  是么?
So, you're Eko, huh?
是的
Yes.
我叫Claire  他是Aaron.
Claire. And this is Aaron.
Aaron?  是圣经里摩西的兄弟?
Aaron? The brother of Moses.
是啊  有点名不符实  是么?
That must've been tough to live up to.
大家会说
Everyone saying,
"为什么你不多像点你兄弟摩西?"
"Why can't you be more like your brother Moses?"
恩  我想是的
I'm sure it was.
你为什么给他起这个名字...
Why did you choose it? Aaron?
Aaron?
只是因为喜欢
I just liked it.
Aaron是个了不起的人
Aaron was a great man.
摩西有语言障碍
Moses had great difficulty speaking,
所以Aaron就成了他的嘴巴
so it was Aaron who spoke for him.
这么说你信教  是么?
So, you're religious, huh?
那你应该和Charlie谈谈
You should speak to Charlie.
他不承认他是信教的
He doesn't want to admit he's religious,
但他总是随身带着一个圣母玛利亚的小雕像
but he carries around a statue of the Virgin Mary.
小雕像?
Statue?
对  他说他是在岛上找到的
Yaah,he said he found it on the island.
很奇怪吧?
Weird, right?
我能看看吗?
May I see it?
他在哪里找到的?
Where did he find this?
他说他是在丛林里找到的
He said he found it in the jungle.
丛林里的哪儿?
Where in the jungle?
-我...我不知道  -快说哪里?
-I don't know.  -Where?
听着  这没什...只是个雕像
Why do you? It's just a statue.
只是个雕像?
Just a statue?
Charlie在哪?
Where is Charlie?
你是闯进去的还是闯出来的?
You breaking in or breaking out?
我以前很喜欢那种老的无声电影
I used to love those old silent movies
强盗把耳朵贴在保险柜边 然后打开密码锁
where the robbers would crack a lock with their ear pressed up against the safe.
他们偷的钱总是装在一个白色口袋里
The money they stole was always in a white bag
口袋上有个大大的美金符号
with a big dollar sign on it.
无声电影?
Silent movies, huh?
你没那么老吧  伙计
You're not that old, man.
我已经够老了
I'm old enough.
在设密码?
You setting the combination?
现在又来了一批人
With the new folks joining us,
我想我们最好限制一下枪的使用权
we better limit people's access to the guns.
不能谁为了一己之私就要给谁用
Can't have just anyone who wants one walk in and help themselves.
我猜你来这就是为了自己的私事吧  Michael
Which, I'm guessing,is why you're here, Michael.
他很聪明  很有魅力 但是当他生气的时候
他会折断你的胳膊  他很有品位
有礼貌并且很有风度 但是当他生气的时候
他会撕烂你的脸  他会给你买首饰
买昂贵的鞋子
嘿  Jin
Hey, Jin.
你喜欢Kinks乐队么?  Kinks?
Jin, do you like The Kinks? Kinks?
膝盖?
Keens?
不不  是Kinks乐队
No, the Kinks.
Kinds的最后一个字母变成"k" K-k-kink-kuh  K-kinks
With a "K" at the end. A kicking "K". "K", Kinks?
你不知道...
You don't...
一旦你被卷入  就不要想再脱身
所以当心点...
很不错的旋律  Jin
It's a good tune.
过来看看
谢谢你  Jin
Thank you very much.
我的嗓子确实很不错  不是吗
I do have a beautiful voice.
你在哪找到这个的?
Where did you find this?
-怎么了?  -你在哪找到的?
-What happened?  -Where did you find it?
在丛林里  我在丛林里找到的
I found it in the jungle.
带我去
Take me there.
这不关你的事
This is not your business.
你在哪儿找到的就带我去哪儿
Take me to where you found it.
好  没问题  对  就算去散散步
Fine. We'll go for a stroll.
那什么都没有
There's nothing there.
我们一早就去  好吗?
In the morning.
我们现在就去
We're going now.
好吧  我去和Claire说一声  好让她别误会
OK. Let me tell Claire, so she doesn't get the wrong idea.
在这儿等我  我去...我们一起去
Wait here. I...Tell her on your way.
弄点啤酒来  快去
Get us some beers. Go.
你在哪找到的?
Where did you find this?
这有关系么?
What does it matter?
另一个袋子里的也一样?
Same in the other bag?
是的
Yes.
5万
Fifty.
什么5万?
Fifty what?
你要我帮你的忙  我给你5万
50 is what I will pay you in exchange for the favour you are asking me to do.
帮忙?
A favour?
你有很多海洛因
You have a large quantity of heroin
但是这个国家既没有罂粟也没有毒品市场
in a country that has no poppies and no market for its sale.
这些毒品在这儿毫无价值
Your drugs are of no value here,
所以你必须把它们运出去
so you must get them out.
但边境都有军队把守
The borders are all guarded by the military,
所以你只能空运
so you must fly.
但是你也知道
But as I am sure you are aware,
现在被允许飞行的私人飞机 要么是运输联合国救援物资的
the only private planes currently allowed into the air
要么就是基督教传教士的飞机
are either UN aid or the Catholic missionaries.
所以你来找我帮你的忙
And so you have come to me for a favour.
我会买你的毒品...5万块
I will buy your heroin.For fifty.
看来传言都是真的
It is true what they say about you.
怎么说?
And what is that?
你不是人
You have no soul.
不
No.
快滚
Go.
滚...
告诉你的朋友是我让你活下来的...
And tell your friends I let you live,
是Eko先生让你活下来的
that Mr.Eko let you live.
就等我一会  好吗?
Just give me a second.
嗨...Claire
Hi... Claire.
那个雕像怎么了?
What happened to the statue?
别装了  Charlie
Don't play stupid.
什么?
What?
这是什么?
What's this?
这是你小雕像里边的东西
Because this was in your little statue.
除非我弄错了
Unless I'm mistaken,
我好像记得你说过你曾经是一个瘾君子
I remember you saying you were a drug addict.
我不知道
I didn't know.
它被密封在这个雕像里边  我怎么会知道?
If it's sealed up inside a statue, how would I know?
Claire  我没有吸毒
Claire? I'm not using.
你现在相信我了吧?
Look. Believe me now?
我不... 在乎
I don't care.
有人在等你
Someone's waiting for you.
会了么?
Got it?
会了
Got it.
好的
All right.
呼出半口气  慢慢的扣下扳机
Breath halfway out,and gently squeeze the trigger.
打...
Squeeze.
好
Good.
你从哪里学的这些?
How'd you learn all this stuff?
我爸爸曾经带我去打猎
My dad used to take me hunting.
打什么?
Hunting for what?
一般是鸟
Birds mostly.
当然了  鸟是不会还击的
Of course, birds don't shoot back.
是啊
Yeah.
我知道人们都在议论
People are talking,
认为我肯定会再去找Walt
thinking I'm gonna go running off after Walt.
有么? 我没听说过
If people are talking,I'm not hearing it.
但如果真是这样 我会说这不是一个明智之举
But if I was, I'd say it's not a very smart plan.
对  没错
Yeah, it's not.
这次来枪真的
Let's try one for real.
好样的
Bravo.
在Claire面前做得不错  伙计
Well done with Claire, mate.
你可给我惹了不少麻烦
You got me in a lot of trouble there,
多谢了啊  希望你开心
so thanks for that.I hope you're happy.
对了  你不会开心的
That's right. You don't do happy.
好了  我们到了
All right. Well, we're here.
我就是在这找到的  那棵树的旁边
I found it right by that tree.
这儿?
You found it here?
对  就在这找到的
Yeah. I found it here.
你在撒谎
You're lying.
我告诉你
Know what?
我根本就不认识你
I don't even know you.
你要看我在哪找到的
You asked to see where I found it.
我就是在这找到的
This is where I found it.
就这样了  祝你开心
We're done. Have a nice hike.
你不是在这找到雕像的
You did not find the statue here.
带我去飞机那
Take me to the plane.
你怎么知道这架飞机?
How did you know about the plane, man?
那已经是很久以前了 它很早就在丛林里了
It's old, you know.Been out in the jungle for years.
当然  你知道的  你什么都知道
Of course, you would know that.You know everything.
你为什么对那个女孩撒谎?
Why did you lie to the girl?
你告诉她你不知道雕像里装的是什么东西
You told her you did not know what was inside the statue.
我没有撒谎
I wasn't lying.
那么什么是误会?
Then what is the wrong idea?
什么?
What?
当我给你看雕像的碎片时
When I showed you the broken pieces of plaster,
你说你不希望她有什么误会
you said you did not want her to get the wrong idea.
是误会什么?
What is the wrong idea?
我不需要什么都说给你知道  伙计
I don't have to tell you anything.
你是长途跋涉穿过了整座岛过来的
You come traipsing across the island
突然  你变头头了?
and suddenly now you're in charge?
你想要我带你去你的飞机那里
You want me to take you to your plane?
你最好开始对我放尊重些
Start treating me with respect.
我不是那种你可以...
I'm not just some guy you can just tr...
什么?
What?
怎么了?
我们走
Let's go.
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
先生  先生  如果你买座雕像
Sir, sir if you buy a statue,
那些钱会给村子用去买脊髓灰质炎的疫苗
the money will buy polio vaccine for the village.
300块  先生
300 naira, sir.
你在这里做什么?
What are you doing here?
我是来忏悔的
I have come to give my confession.
你好  Eko
Hello, Eko.
你好  兄弟
Hello, Brother.
3年里我第一次来看你
I come to visit you for the first time in three years
而你却不听我的忏悔吗?
and you won't hear my confession?
你知道  神主曾经说过
Monsignor would have said he'd failed
他没能成功地培养天主教的孩子
to raise a proper Catholic boy.
好了  干嘛浪费你的时间忏悔呢? 对你没用的
Why waste your time confessing?It won't help you.
没用?
It won't?
是的  忏悔是有意义的
No.For confession to mean something,
你一定要有颗虔诚的心
you must have a penitent heart.
忏悔你和你的罪行吧  Yemi
You and your guilt, Yemi.
我这么做只是为了生存
I've only done what I needed to do to survive.
那怎么是罪行?
How is that a sin?
你可以远离这里生活
You may live far from here,
但是那不代表我没听说过你是怎么一个人
but I have heard of who you are
和你做过什么
and what you have done.
你忘了那天你是怎么面临抉择的么  兄弟?
Have you forgotten how you got that cross,
他们带走我的那天...
the day they took me?
那天我做的有罪吗  还是说可以被原谅
Is what I did that day a sin?Or is it forgiven,
因为我救的是你
because it is you that was saved?
你为什么来这  Eko?
Why are you here, Eko?
我来帮助你
I've come to help you.
我有一些货物需要运出国
I have some merchandise that I need to get out of the country.
我想用你教会的一架飞机来运输
I would like one of your church relief flights to transport it.
"货物"?  你指毒品
Merchandise. You mean drugs.
那和我往常的生意不一样  Yemi
It is not my normal business.
我们要把毒品运出尼日利亚
We are moving the drugs out of Nigeria
这样可以使我们的人民远离毒品
so that they cannot be used by our people.
至于钱...
And you will have all the money
你可以拿所有的钱买疫苗
to buy your vaccine.
上帝给了我们这个机会
God has given us this opportunity.
我们不应该放过它
We should not turn our back on it.
上帝并没有要你来这里  Eko
God did not bring you here, Eko.
是你的贪婪带你来的
Your own greed did.
我会永远爱你...
I will always love you,
但我不会帮助你
but I will not help you.
很高兴再见到你  兄弟
It was good to see you again, Brother.
再靠耳朵一点  小姐
Little close to the ear.
你知道你在做什么么?
Sure you know what you're doing?
你可以把头转开吗?
Would you please turn your head?
为什么?  这样你就可以往我脖子上开一枪?
You ain't got a clean enough shot at my neck?
我可以自己理发
I can cut my own damn hair.
你知道  你不必要只是为了说话而说话
You don't have to be belligerent just for belligerence's sake.
现在每个人都喜欢你
Everyone loves you now.
瞎说
Bull pucky.
哟  Sawyer  欢迎你回来
Yo, Sawyer.Glad you're back, man.
看好你自己吧  药丸子
Yo yourself, Pillsbury.
了解了?
You see?
嘿  Kate...
Hey, Kate...
Locke说你一会要去仓子里轮班
Locke said you're on hatch duty later.
我在想是否...你不介意我替你去吧
I was wondering...You mind if I go instead?
你想代我当班?
You want my shift?
可以让我想些事情
Help me take my mind off things.
当然  你去吧
Sure, it's all yours.
谢谢  非常感谢
Thanks. Appreciate it.
很高兴你复原了  伙计
Glad you're OK, man.
恩
Yeah.
别提了
Don't even say it.
好了  是时间休息一下了
All right. Time to take a break.
我们刚刚才休息过
Just had a break.
我并不是你想象的那样
I'm not what you think I am.
我想象你是什么?
What do I think you are?
那都是我兄弟的错
It was my brother's fault.
什么?
Sorry?
我成为瘾君子是他的错
It was his fault I became an addict.
他开始吸毒  我试着阻止他
He started with the heroin.I tried to make him stop.
你并不了解  我是个好人
You don't know me, man.I was a good person.
我曾是神父的助手
I was an altar boy.
好了  我知道雕像里有什么
I knew what was in that statue.
那不意味着我需要这些东西
It doesn't mean I needed it.
所以别拿这些来评判我
So don't judge me, man.
别...
Don't... Just...
什么?
What?
那是什么?
What's that?
一个降落伞
It's a parachute.
那是个牧师?
Is that a priest?
你在做什么?
What're you doing?
你认识这人?
Do you know that guy?
是的
Yes.
这个人救了我的命
This man saved my life.
救了你的命  啊? 是啊  很合情合理
Saved your life, huh? Sure, that makes sense.
他在尼日利亚的一个平原起飞 而我们在南太平洋的中间
He takes off in a plane in Nigeria.We're in the South Pacific.
那简直太合情理了
That makes all the sense in the world.
这是经文
This is scripture written here.
你是个牧师  你是个牧师  是吗?
You're a priest, right?
他是个牧师  你也是  对吗?
He's a priest and you're a priest, too, right?
我需要和你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
我正在听他的忏悔
I'm in the middle of a confession.
没时间等了
It cannot wait.
上帝保佑你
God bless you.
上帝与你同在  请早上再来
God be with you all.Please, come back in the morning.
没事的
It's OK.
你怎么敢来这里打扰我的工作
How dare you disrupt my work?
-你重新考虑过了吗? -什么?
-Have you reconsidered my request?  -What?
我的要求
My request
在教会的掩护下运送毒品?
Flying drugs under the cover of the Church?
我怎么可能考虑这种事情?
How could I ever reconsider?
听着  别碰那些东西
Don't touch those.
这件事办起来很简单
I am going to make this easy for you.
你让我们假扮成牧师 我们会自己把毒品运出去
You will make us priests and we will fly the drugs out.
让你们假扮成牧师?
Make you priests?
在这些任命文件上签字
Sign these ordination documents.
我就会给你买疫苗的钱
I will give you the money for the vaccines.
马上给我离开教堂  Eko
Leave this church now.
马上给我走
Go. Now.
Yemi  我理解你生活在一个
Yemi, I understand that you live in a world
正邪分明的世界
where righteousness and evil seem very far apart,
但那并不是真正的世界
but that is not the real world.
我是你的兄弟而且我永远不会伤害你
I am your brother,I would never do anything to hurt you,
但是我的朋友...如果你不照我说的干
but my friends,if you do not do what I ask,
他们会烧光这座教堂
they will burn this church to the ground.
这还不值得你在这纸上签个名么?
Is that worth less than the price of your name on a piece of paper?
想想你可以拯救的生命
Think of the lives you will save.
我的签名并不会让你们成为牧师  Eko
My signature does not make you a priest.
你永远不会成为牧师
You could never be a priest.
你们剩下多少雕像
How many of the statues do you have left
圣母玛利亚的雕像  还有多少?
How many of the Virgin Mary statues do you have left?
呃...300个
I've 300.
我全要了
I will take all of them.
我想我们现在都是有罪的了
I guess we are both sinners now.
也许我们是的  但是上帝会原谅我的  Eko
Perhaps we are,but God will forgive me.
我迷路了
I'm lost.
当时很黑  我跟着Sayid
It was dark. I was following Sayid.
头被什么东西砸了一下
A big bag of rocks fell on my head.
所以我很抱歉我对地理不太感冒
I'm sorry if I'm a bit spotty with the geography.
爬到树上去
Climb that tree.
什么?
What?
爬上那棵树也许你就会有点方向感了
Perhaps you will get your bearings
或许会看到飞机
or see the plane.
爬上去
You climb it.
如果我不去呢?
What if I don't?
你会用你的圣经棒打我?
You going to beat me with your Jesus stick?
我觉得有点奇怪  你的棒子上有血迹
I find it odd that your scripture stick has dried blood on it.
你到底爬不爬?
Are you going to climb that tree or not?
你到底是个什么牧师?
What kind of priest are you, anyway?
你要再爬高点
You need to get higher.
很好  谢谢
Wonderful. Thank you.
Eko  跑  快跑
Eko! Run! Run!
你看见了吗?
Did you see it?
是的  我看见了  你傻愣着干什么?
What the bloody hell did you do?
我什么也没干
I did nothing.
大多数人  当他们看见黑烟形成的东西都会跑
When most people see a creature made of swirling black smoke, they run.
-我并不害怕那个东西  -我看的出来
-I was not afraid of it.  -I can see that.
-那个东西会杀人  -你看见飞机了吗?
-That thing kills people.  -Did you see the plane?
是的  看见了  它在那个方向一公里处
It's about a kilometre that way.
谢谢
Thank you.
等等
Wait.
拜托
Come on.
你在哪里?
Where are you?
爸爸?
你还好吗?
我很好  谢谢
你一个人吗?
是的
不能说很久  他们就要回来了
你在哪里?
你得来...
嘿  Michael
Hey, Michael.
你怎么样?
How you doing?
很好  谢谢
I'm good, thanks.
你一个人在这里?
You down here alone?
恩  Hurley也应该在这里
Hurley's supposed to be here.
但是  呃  我想他来晚了
But I guess he's running late.
好吧  听着  呃...
Well, listen, uh...
没人会忘了Walt
No one's forgotten about Walt.
-什么?  -我不能...
-What?  -I can't...
我完全不知道你们将经历什么
I don't have any idea what you must be going through.
但是我要你知道我们会尽快
I just want you to know that as soon as we can,
找到他在哪儿
we're gonna figure out a way to go out
然后把他带回来
and bring him back.
恩  谢谢  伙计
Yeah.Thanks, man.
谢谢
Thanks.
你还好吧?
You OK?
是的  我很好
Yeah. I'm fine.
恩  那就拜托你了
I'll leave you to it, then.
谢谢
Thanks.
Eko
你来这干什么  Yemi?
What are you doing here, Yemi?
我来阻止你
I came to stop you.
回你的教堂去
Go to your church.
别上飞机  Eko
Do not get on that plane.
你救过我一次  现在我是来救你的
I'm here to save your life.
救我?
Save my life?
听着  如果你上了飞机  如果你这么做了...
If you get on, if you do this...
如果我做了什么  Yemi? 你现在是预言家?
If I do what? Are you a prophet now?
拜托  Eko 我听你的忏悔
Please, let me take your confession.
任何我能做的事我都会做  但是  请不要走
Anything I can do, I will do. But please, don't go.
他向军方告发了
He told the military.
是你做的?
You did this?
我并没有告诉他们谁牵涉其中
I did not tell them who was involved.
离开那些毒品和我一起回去
Just leave the drugs and come back with me.
不  停下  别开枪了
Stop. No more.
Yemi  Yemi  Yemi
不  不  不
No  No  No
帮我抱住他
Help me get him in.
Yemi
神父?
Father?
你还好吧  神父?
Are you OK, Father?
Eko?
那是谁?
Who's that?
他是我的兄弟
He's my brother.
我很难过
I'm sorry.
还你一个
For the one I broke.
你是一个牧师么?
So, are you a priest or aren't you?
是的  我是
Yes, I am.
耶和华是我的牧者  我必不至缺乏
The Lord is my shepherd. I shall not want.
他让我躺在青青的草地上
He maketh me to lie down in green pastures.
领我在可静静的水边
He leadeth me beside the still waters.
他使我的灵魂苏醒
He restoreth my soul.
以他的名义引导我正义的道路
He leadeth me in the paths of righteousness for his name's sake.
尽管我漫步死亡峡谷的阴影中
Yea, though I walk through the shadow of the valley of death,
我将不会害怕任何魔鬼  因为你与我同在
I fear no evil, for thou art with me.
你的杖  你的竿  都安慰着我
Thy rod, thy staff, they comfort me.
在我敌人面前
Thou preparest a table before me
你为我摆设筵席
in the presence of mine enemies,
你用油膏涂了我的头
thou annointest my head with oil,
使我福杯满溢
my cup runneth over.
我一生一世
Surely goodness and mercy shall follow me,
必有恩惠慈爱随着我
all the days of my life,
我而且要住在耶和华的殿中
and I will dwell in the house
直到永远
of the Lord forever.
阿门
Amen.
Claire?
你骗我  Charlie
You lied to me, Charlie.
我知道
I know I did.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
这...这会让我感觉更安全
It just made me feel safer to have it around.
听着  我不能让你守着我的孩子  好么?
I can't have you around my baby.
Claire  我不...
Claire, I...
Charlie  我不想要你睡在我们附近 可以么?
I don't want you sleeping anywhere near us.
走吧
Just go.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====